[Music]
Hi, everyone, I'm Molly Wright,
a junior from Memphis, Tennessee,
and I'm this year's
Director of Philanthropy.
Tri Delta's national philanthropy is
St. Jude Children's Research Hospital.
When a patient goes to St. Jude,
their family never
receives a bill for their
child's lifesaving care.
Tri Delta places a housing
facility on St. Jude's campus where
families and patients can stay
during their time at St. Jude.
I'm incredibly proud to be
a part of a chapter that
focuses its ideals on such
an important organization.
I'm Ann Morgan Sanders. I'm from
Tupelo, Mississippi, and when I was
just a year old, I was diagnosed
with acute lymphoblastic leukemia.
Going through recruitment,
Tri Delta's philanthropy really resonated
with me because of my own
personal experience with St. Jude.
As recruitment week went on,
I kept thinking
back to Tri Delta's
philanthropy and thinking
about how if I went Tri Delt,
I would be getting
to give back to the place
that gave me so much.
Even though I was diagnosed at such
a young age, St. Jude still means so much
to me because without their lifesaving
treatment, I wouldn't be here today.
Hey, everyone, my name is Kylie Branian.
I'm from Nashville, Tennessee.
When I was 16 years old, I was diagnosed
with a high-risk type
of cancer called neuroblastoma.
After my diagnosis,
my family and I had to look
at numerous places to receive treatment.
We decided that St. Jude was
the perfect place for me.
When I got to St. Jude,
the first place that my family
and I stayed was the Tri Delta
Place on St. Jude's campus.
For a little under two years,
I went through numerous
rounds of chemotherapy, radiation,
transplants and surgery.
The nurses and staff at St. Jude helped
me through some of my hardest days,
even though I wasn't able
to be home very often.
Little did I know, three years
later, I'd be sitting here
today next to someone who shares
such a similar story to me.
Throughout the year,
we host several different
fundraising events to raise
money for St. Jude.
Not only are we raising
money and saving lives,
but we're also bonding with our sisters.
One of our biggest
fundraising events is DHOP,
which we hold each year
at the Tri Delta house.
DHOP is our pancake breakfast
where all our members sell
tickets to the students on
campus and the Oxford community.
This event is so fun because
all members of the community
get to come out to the house
to support our philanthropy.
In the spring, we host our annual
letter-writing campaign where all
our members ask their friends
and families for donations to St. Jude.
One good thing about being so
close to Memphis is that so many
of us got to participate
in the St. Jude Half Marathon this year.
I, along with so many
others, had the honor
of running through St. Jude
campus in December.
One unique event that we
get to host at the Chi
chapter is our Shirley Crawford
Tennis Tournament.
It's so amazing to see so many people
come out to support our beloved alum,
Shirley Crawford, and to support
our philanthropy, St. Jude.
When Tri Delta first made its
partnership with St. Jude,
we committed to raising
$60 million in 10 years.
And I'm so excited to tell
you all that this past year,
we reached that goal two years early.
[Music]